Han Li

60 Market Street Melbourne, VIC 3000

Email: Han.li1223@outlook.com Mobile:0413 651 083

CAREER OBJECTIVES

Passionate and dynamic Hospitality Management graduate and currently studying in master's degree of Data Science. Aiming to use my knowledge and experiences in the industry to achieve professional and personal growth and to contribute to the objectives of the organisation.

PROFESSIONAL STRENGTHS

- Energetic, outgoing personality, attention to details
- Excellent communication skills with a good understanding of cross-cultural teams and the ability to speak fluent Mandarin and Cantonese.
- Excellent customer service skills and multi-tasking ability.
- Perform well under pressure and able to work and leading a team.
- Advance level in data analysis method and tools including Microsoft Excel, R, Python,
 SQL and Tableau

EDUCATION BACKGROUND

Master of Data Science

Monash University, Victoria Melbourne

07/2021 - Current

Bachelor of Hospitality Management

Holmesglen Institute, Victoria Melbourne

06/2016 - 06/2019

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

The Como Mgallary South Yarra

Guest Service Agent/ Duty Manager / Reservation Supervisor(secondment)

February 2021 - Current

- Liaise with all related department to ensure every guest and group has a smooth arrival experience. Flag VIP guest information, preferences, and instructions within related team members
- Provide efficient and friendly service for all guests and respond to guest complaint.
- Respond to all general guest enquiries via E-mail, telephone and facsimile within the requested period and maintain the brand standard.
- Provide support and training to team member.
- Liaise with director of sale and revenue to provide demand insight, assist in creating monthly forecasts

Pullman & Mercure Melbourne Albert Park

Inbound Reservation Sales Agent

January 2020 - February 2021

- Processing reservations and related enquiry from multiple channels
- Liaise with all related department to ensure every guest and group has a smooth arrival experience. Flag VIP guest information, preferences, and instructions within related team colleagues
- Respond to all general guest enquiries via E-mail, Telephone and Facsimile within the requested period and maintain the brand standard.
- Negotiate with all inbound enquiries for accommodation, event, and F&B, follow up with payment and data input for further performance analysis.

Sheraton Melbourne Hotel

Reservations Agent

November 2018 – January 2019, June 2019 – January 2020

- Processing reservations and related enquiry from multiple channels.
- Assist reservation manager in inventory control by balancing inventory and managing overbooking, prepare requested report including daily pick up and competitor benchmarking.
- Close communication with all related department to ensure every guest has a smooth arrival experience. Share special guest information, preferences and instructions within related team colleagues.
- Respond to all general FIT guest enquiries via E-mail, Telephone Facsimile or other require method within the requested period.
- Collect requested information and assist the revenue department to conduct price and marketing related analysis.

Fourpoints By Sheraton Dockland Melbourne (Internship)

Revenue Management/Reservation Intern

August 2018- November 2018

- Assisted with integration and system switch for Starwood to Marriott across 3 large scale properties.
- Expose to related property management systems for hotel operation and revenue management.
- Assisting Supervisors to prepare all requested report including benching marking and daily performance report.
- Assist with general reservations agent's role including daily arrival check, investigate open guest account or ad-hoc task assigned by the management team.

 Assist revenue manager to monitor demand and provide insight for pricing strategy.
REFERENCE
On Request